ILGWU. James Lipsig papers, 5780/082
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II. General files, 1949-1976
  - Federation of Union Representatives. Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Federation of Union Representatives. Miscellaneous, 1961-1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - ILGWU and Federation of Union Representatives. Report on Challenged Ballots, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Federation of Union Representatives. Literature and Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Union Representatives. Literature and Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - IGLWU and Federation of Union Representatives. Report on Challenged Ballots, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Federation of Union Representatives. Campaign Materials, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Federation of Union Representatives. Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Federal Legislation, 1950-1954 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Griffiths, George F., 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Health and Welfare Funds. Regulations, 1948-1954 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. Correspondence and Memos, 1950-1956 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. Miscellaneous, 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. Report by the Anti-Discrimination Department, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. Anti-Discrimination Department, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. Sharkey-Brown-Isaacs Law, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. New York Panel Correspondence, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. Civil Rights Materials, 1955-1959 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. National Trade Union Council for Human Rights, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. New York Civil Rights Affairs [folder 1 of 2], 1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. New York Civil Rights Affairs [folder 2 of 2], 1960 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. Organized Rallies, Panels and Meetings, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. News clips, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. Meeting Announcements and Minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Labor Committee. Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Jurisdictional Department, IGLWU [folder 1 of 3], 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Jurisdictional Department, ILGWU [folder 2 of 3], 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Jurisdictional Department, ILGWU [folder 3 of 3], 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Labor Investigation Department, IGLWU. Correspondence, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - League for Industrial Democracy. Correspondence, 1948-1954 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Liberal Party of New York. Correspondence., 1955-1964 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Local 89, Italian Dressmakers' Union Correspondence, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Local 155. Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Local 155. Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Local 155. Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Local 155. Correspondence, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Local 155. Protest-Appeal of Edward J. Tucker, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Matheson, Minnie. Correspondence, 1947-1958 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Montreal Building Mortgage Loan, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Meeting Notices and Memos, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Committee on Immigration Materials, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Correspondence with James Lipsig, 1949-1956 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Meetings, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Joint Program Plan for Jewish Community Relations, 1959- 1960 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Memorandums [folder 1 of 2], 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Memorandums [folder 2 of 2], 1957 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - National Community Advisory Council. Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Civil Liberties Memorandums, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Subcommittee on Constitutional Rights, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Committee on Immigration, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Senate Subcommittee Hearings on Immigration [folder 1 of 2], 1948 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Senate Subcommittee Hearings on Immigration [folder 2 of 2], 1948 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 1 of 4], 1948 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 2 of 4], 1948 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 3 of 4], 1948 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 4 of 4], 1948 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 1 of 2], 1949 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 2 of 2], 1949 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 1 of 8], 1949 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 2 of 8], 1949 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 3 of 8], 1949 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 4 of 8], 1949 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 5 of 8], 1949 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 6 of 8], 1950 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 7 of 8], 1950 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council. Legislative Information Committee [folder 8 of 8], 1950 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - National Child Labor Committee. Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund. Correspondence and Reports [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund. Correspondence and Reports [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund. Correspondence and Reports [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Union New Jersey Health Center. Correspondence and Manuals, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - New Jersey Unemployment Commission and ILG Health and Vacation Funds. Correspondence, 1946- 1948 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - New York State Ladies Garment Workers Center [folder 1 of 3], 1922-1966 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - New York State Ladies Garment Center [folder 2 of 3], 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - New York State Ladies Garment Center [folder 3 of 3], 1921-1926 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - New York Legislation Correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - New York Federation of Labor. Correspondence, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - New York Legislation Memos and Analyses, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - New York State Health and Welfare Fund. Correspondence, 1962-1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Insurance and Retirement Benefits Funds Materials, 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Report on Examination of the Welfare and Severance Fund, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Welfare Fund Bureau Correspondence and Summaries, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Northeast Department. Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Northeast Department. Health and Welfare Materials, 1949-1950 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Lipsig, James. Personal Correspondence [folder 1 of 3], 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Lipsig, James. Personal Correspondence [folder 2 of 3], 1956-1960 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Lipsig, James. Personal Correspondence [folder 3 of 3], 1954-1957 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Political Department. Notices and Campaign Materials [folder 1 of 2], 196-1965 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Political Department. Notices and Campaign Materials [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Powell Investigations of the Garment Industry [folder 1 of 5], 1962 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Powell Investigations of the Garment Industry [folder 2 of 5], 1962-1964 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Powell Investigations of the Garment Industry [folder 3 of 5], 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Powell Investigations in the Garment Industry [folder 4 of 5], 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Powell Investigations in the Garment Industry [folder 5 of 5], 1962-1965 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Powell Investigations in the Garment Industry. Newspaper Clippings, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - New York State Power Authority Act Materials, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - New York State Power Authority. Niagara Power Development, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - New York State Power Authority. St. Lawrence Power Project, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - New York State Liberal Party. State Legislation Program, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - New York State Power Projects. St. Lawrence and Niagara Rivers, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - New York State Power Authority. Statements and Hearings, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - New York State Power Authority. Miscellaneous Project Materials, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - New York State Power Authority. Progress Information on the Niagara Project, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Reciprocity Retirement Fund [folder 1 of 3], 1951-1956 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Reciprocity Retirement Fund [folder 2 of 3], 1951-1956 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Reciprocity Retirement Fund [folder 3 of 3], 1951-1956 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Death Benefit Fund. ILGWU Agreement with Goodman Block, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - ILGWU Officer's Retirement Fund Trust, 1946-1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Roosevelt College Deposit Agreement, American National Escrow [folder 1 of 4], 1951 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Roosevelt College Deposit Agreement, American National Escrow [folder 2 of 4], 1951-1959 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Roosevelt College Deposit Agreement, American National Escrow [folder 3 of 4], 1955-1961 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Roosevelt College Deposit Agreement, American National Escrow [folder 4 of 4], 1951-1955 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Sedares, Constantine. Discharge Process Materials [folder 1 of 3], 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Sedares, Constantine. Discharge Process Materials [folder 2 of 3], 1961 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Sedares, Constantine. Discharge Process Materials [folder 3 of 3], 1961 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Socialist Party. Minutes, Reports and Correspondence [folder 1 of 5], 1948-1950 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Party. Minutes, Reports and Correspondence [folder 2 of 5], 1947-1949 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Socialist Party. Minutes, Reports and Correspondence [folder 3 of 5], 1946-1957 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Socialist Party. Minutes, Reports and Correspondence [folder 4 of 5], 1955 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Party. Minutes, Reports and Correspondence [folder 5 of 5], 1950-1952 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - ILGWU Staff Retirement Fund. Financial Statements and Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Joint Board Dress and Waistmakers' Union. Reinstatement of Firms and Strike Materials, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Steel Strike Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Union Health Center. Minutes, Memos and Reports [folder 1 of 9], 1958 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Union Health Center. Minutes, Memos and Reports [folder 2 of 9], 1955 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Union Health Center. Minutes, Memos and Reports [folder 3 of 9], 1953-1958 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Union Health Center. Minutes, Memos and Reports [folder 4 of 9], 1948-1960 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Union Health Center. Minutes, Memos and Reports [folder 5 of 9], 1956-1958 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Union Health Center. Minutes, Memos and Reports [folder 6 of 9], 1955-1968 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Union Health Center. Minutes, Memos and Reports [folder 7 of 9], 1955-1964 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Union Health Center. Minutes, Memos and Reports [folder 8 of 9], 1960-1961 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Union Health Center. Minutes, Memos and Reports [folder 9 of 9], 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - GEB Union Health Center Committee Minutes, 1964-1966 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Union Health Center and Local 153 Contract Correspondence [folder 1 of 3], 1953 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Union Health Center and Local 153 Contract Correspondence [folder 3 of 3], 1947-1953 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Union Health Center and Local 153 Contract Correspondence [folder 3 of 3], 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Union Health Center and Nurses Guild Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1950 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Union Health Center and Nurses Guild Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1947-1950 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Union Health Center and Nurses Guild Correspondence [folder 1 of 3], 1951-1956 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Union Health Center and Nurses Guild Correspondence [folder 2 of 3], 1951-1956 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Union Health Center and Nurses Guild Correspondence [folder 3 of 3], 1951-1956 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Union for Democratic Socialism Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1953-1956 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Union for Democratic Socialism Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1953-1956 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Union House Committee. Minutes, Memos and Correspondence, 1952-1956 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Unity House. Accident Report [folder 1 of 6], 1963-1970 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Unity House. Accident Report [folder 2 of 6], 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Unity House. Accident Report [folder 3 of 6], 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Unity House. Accident Report [folder 4 of 6], 1963 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Unity House. Accident Report [folder 5 of 6], 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Unity House. Accident Report [folder 6 of 6], 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Unity House. Cabaret Tax Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Unity House Committee Miscellaneous, 1952-1954 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Series III. Directives and form letters
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter A [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter A [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1967 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letters A-B, 1961-1967 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter C [folder 1 of 6], 1958-1969 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter C [folder 2 of 6], 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter C [folder 3 of 3], 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter C [folder 4 of 6], 1951-1964 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter C [folder 5 of 6], 1961-1965 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter C [folder 6 of 6], 1947-1971 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter D [folder 1 of 5], 1958-1969 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter D [folder 2 of 5], 1951-1958 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter D [folder 3 of 5], 1950-1969 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter D [folder 4 of 5], 1952-1966 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter D [folder 5 of 5], 1952-1960 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter E [folder 1 of 2], 1954-1967 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter E [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1967 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter E, 1958-1961 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter G, 1951-1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter H [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1968 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter H [folder 2 of 2], 1954-1967 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter I [folder 1 of 6], 1962-1966 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter I [folder 2 of 6], 1950-1963 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter I [folder 3 of 6], 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter I [folder 4 of 6], 1957-1962 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter I [folder 5 of 6], 1957-1961 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter I [folder 6 of 6], 1951-1957 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter J, 1946-1964 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter L [folder 1 of 4], 1960-1967 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter L [folder 2 of 4], 1951-1964 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter L [folder 3 of 4], 1949-1969 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter L [folder 4 of 4], 1955-1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter M [folder 1 of 4], 1961-1967 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter M [folder 2 of 4], 1953-1961 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter M [folder 3 of 4], 1941-1963 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter M [folder 4 of 4], 1941-1962 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter N, 1954-1967 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter O, 1947-1967 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter P [folder 1 of 2], 1950-1970 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter P [folder 2 of 2], 1952-1970 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter R [folder 1 of 6], 1959-1968 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter R [folder 2 of 6], 1950-1970 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter R [folder 3 of 6], 1956-1964 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter R [folder 4 of 6], 1954-1957 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter R [folder 5 of 6], 1953-1961 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter R [folder 6 of 6], 1947-1967 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter S [folder 1 of 2], 1953-1964 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter S [folder 2 of 2], 1946-1966 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter T [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1966 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter T [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1968 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter U [folder 1 of 4], 1954-1968 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter U [folder 2 of 4], 1947-1967 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter U [folder 3 of 4], 1956-1965 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter U [folder 4 of 4], 1947-1961 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter W [folder 1 of 2], 1956-1966 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - ILGWU Organization Issues. Letter W [folder 2 of 2], 1954-1966 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Department Notices., 1974-1977 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Department Notices., 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Department Notices., 1967-1971 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Department Notices., 1965-1970 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Series IV. Legal appeals and cases
  - Ames, Arnold. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Appel, Israel. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Barbarino v. James. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1959-1961 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Barco, Harry. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1957-1959 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Benigno, Joseph. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Bernstein, Sarah. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Bloom, Isidor. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Bruzzone, Mary. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Buchwald, Julius. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Canadian Appeal Cases. [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1968 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    French and English
  - Canadian Appeal Cases. [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Canadian Appeal Cases. [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1968 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Cohen, Bernard. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Crowley, John. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Dans, Morris. Correspondences. Re: Appeal, 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Ebert, Allen. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Los Angeles Election Materials and Affidavits, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Local 38 Election Materials, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Elias, Murray. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Fertel, Nathan. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Fine, Isidore. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Furino, Joseph. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Girlando, Joseph and Morris Shuman. Case of Appeal, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Goldstein, Morris. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    English and Yiddish
  - Jacobs, Christabel. V. Barbarino, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Kandell, Harry. Correspondence. Re: Appeal [folder 1 of 3], 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Kandell, Harry. Correspondence. Re: Appeal [folder 2 of 3], 1949-1959 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Kandell, Harry. Correspondence. Re: Appeal [folder 3 of 3], 1959 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Kaufman, William. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Kline, Leo. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1959-1962 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Levitt, Herbert. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - McSwan, Charles. Case of Appeal Materials, 1962-1963 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Martinot, Steve. Case of Appeal Materials, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Muggeo, Benjamino. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Ostrov, Morris. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Pankin, Battina. Trust Agreement and Correspondence, 1958-1968 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Perry, Hilda. Grievance and Appeal [folder 1 of 3], 1963 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Perry, Hilda. Grievance and Appeal [folder 2 of 3], 1963 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Perry, Hilda. Grievance and Appeal [folder 3 of 3], 1963 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Piazza, Salvatore. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Proverman, Morris. Grievance and Appeal, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Reisman, Rose. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Research Department. Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Schindler, Harry. Special Trial Committee and Appeal, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Seid, Arthur. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1962-1965 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Shuman, Morris. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Shwager, Abraham. Case of Appeal Materials, 1957-1959 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Simone, Tom. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1952-1959 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Spica, Josephine. Case of Appeal [folder 1 of 2], 1954-1957 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Spica, Josephine. Case of Appeal [folder 2 of 2], 1954 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Taubman, Morris. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Thompson, Sidney. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Thompson v. Mirgon. Case Materials, 1957-1959 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Case of Appeal for Tucker, Tucker and Malloy, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Veneto, Andrew. Case of Appeal Materials, 1963-1965 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Villano, William and Frank Bagolie. Cases of Appeal, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Weis, Mary. Trust Agreement, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Zalowitz, Sarah. Correspondence. Re: Appeal, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 8)